// Questions for Math
const QBANK_MATH = [
  {
    prompt: "-5 + (-11) = ?",
    options: ["-14", "-16", "16", "-6"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "10 + (-22) = ?",
    options: ["12", "-12", "10", "-10"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "-5 - (-5) = ?",
    options: ["10", "-10", "55", "0"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Evaluate x - y if x = -3 and y = -4",
    options: ["-7", "7", "1", "-1"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The distance between -4 and 5 is",
    options: ["1", "9", "-1", "-9"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Evaluate ab if a = -6 and b = -5",
    options: ["-11", "30", "-30", "11"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Evaluate y/x if y = -10, x = 2",
    options: ["-20", "-10", "-5", "10"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Evaluate -4(3) + (-7)",
    options: ["-19", "19", "0", "10"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The additive inverse of -4 is",
    options: ["0", "4", "1", "-4"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "0.3 in fraction form is",
    options: ["3/10", "3/1", "1/3", "10/3"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "If x = -3, y = 5, evaluate x - y",
    options: ["-2", "2", "-8", "8"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "0.7 in fractional form is",
    options: ["1/7", "7/1", "7/10", "7/9"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "0.777... (repeating) in fraction form is",
    options: ["1/7", "7/1", "7/10", "7/9"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The distance between -2 and 5 is",
    options: ["0", "-8", "7", "-7"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The additive inverse of -0.25 is",
    options: ["0.25", "-2", "-0.25", "25"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
];
